# **Donald Aubert**

### Proposal, Test, RF and / or Communications Systems engineer

Mount Laurel, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Donald-Aubert/1c7aa2809aadaa44

Satellite System Engineer, with RF component and subsystems (payload and TT&C) experience. More than 20 years of related experience including: satellite communications system engineering architecture development, technical support for proposals, design, manufacturing, test and mission operations.

Detail oriented. provided successful technical support for imixed RF/digital subsystem throughout complete product life cycle (from architecture development to mission operations.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Lead Comm Systems Engineer, Secure Telemetry Tracking and Command (STT&C) MUOS Program - September 2002 to March 2014

## Certified Product Engineer, Secure Telemetry Tracking and Command Subsystem

Lockheed Martin - Newtown, PA - 1992 to 2002

for MUOS Military Satellite throughout complete 11-year life cycle, including: proposal, PDR, CDR, Test Procedures, Satellite Satellite Test, and Mission Operations. Successful product deliveries included five payload modules and support: launch, transfer orbit On Orbit Test and Post-Handover support for two MUOS spacecraft.

Payload Comm Systems Engineer, 1992 to 2002 providing technical support for:

- Satellite comm. payloads for Proposals, including: GE Americom, SBIRS, Gapfiller, GOES,
- Development phases of satellite communication payloads for SBIRS and EOS programs
- Manufacturing phase of DSCS program

#### RF Group Unit Manager

IR&D for - 1982 to 1992

lead a group of engineers in the development and manufacture of transmitters and receivers for communications satellites

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **MBA** in Management of Operating Systems

Drexel University - Philadelphia, PA 1979

#### Master of Science in Electrical Engineering

University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA 1974

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

#### **SKILLS**

STT&C / payload architecture design and analysis Test Program Development: Unit, Satellite, OOT levels Satellite / Unit Specification Development & Test Procedure Development

Spec flowdown (/ up) Satellite <> Component Level Resolved test issues at component and Spacecraft levels

Excel-based Comm. Systems Analysis Mission Operations support (e.g. launch, on orbit test, post hand over)